hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Kowski in this podcast we talk
about how coaches mentors and trainers
can scale their businesses to make the
kind of money that they want to make
online listen I meet a lot of coaches
they got a lot of great material a lot
of great stuff that they can help people
with but they don't know how to get
clients they don't know how to actually
close the sale so that's what we're
going to be talking about here today is
what I believe is the three-step process
to attracting more clients for you and
this breaks down simply like the step
number one you want want to know where
to find the right people step number two
we need to promote our offer to those
people and then step number three we
need to close the sale and anytime that
you are selling courses coaching
mentoring these steps work finding the
right people is about where do they
exist where are you going to find
them on social media is one of the best
ways to find people on YouTube you can
also do so going to seminars or by doing
uh joint ventures with people where they
can give you referrals but what I find
is that social media is one of the best
ways to do this and then what we need to
do is we need to learn how to tap into
the algorithm to be able to show our
information to the right people and this
means aligning our messaging to who we
can help the most a coaching business an
online course business is one of the
best ways to make six and S figures no
matter what you've done or what your
experience is you sharing with people
what you have experience in is one of
the best ways to monetize your following
online if you're an influencer or
somebody who is doing that type of a
thing so if you want to attract clients
to any kind of a business having a
coaching business is important for this
and we want to find where are those
people and it's based on the way that
the algorithms work nowadays whether
you're running paid advertising or
they're
organic is that it's going based on
people's behaviors on these apps on
Instagram it's one of our favorite ones
that we like using on Tik Tok on
Facebook on LinkedIn whatever somebody
is interacting with let's say that this
is your potential client every single
person has a profile that these apps
have built on them and it shows content
based on what it knows their interests
are but also very nuanced what are they
paying attention to right now this week
even today your algorithm and your news
feed can change from day to day based on
what interests you what pequs your
interest and it knows how to grab on to
all of that especially when it comes to
people that you're looking to reach so
to find those people we got to figure
out okay how do we hone in on the exact
right person who is going to do two
things number one they're going to get
results with what we offer if you're a
coach or course grader the most
important thing you can do is generating
results for people the reason why I do
what I do is because we generate massive
results for people people have told us
this over the years and I continue to do
this because I love seeing people's
lives changed but from there you can tap
into the algorithms on social media to
actually show your content or to show
your paid advertising which is even
better because you can pay to put
yourself in front of the right people at
scale I can maybe hope the algorithm
shows my content to some people on a
viral post but if I push that with an
Instagram ad I can show it to tens of
thousands of people for pennies on the
dollar and so that's one of the best
ways to do that and then that's where we
want to promote our offers not just
promote who we are but promote what we
offer so you want to take okay here's my
coaching here's the solution here's the
transformation here's the result that I
can deliver to people and I want to
promote that to these people that I know
are the ones that are looking for that
kind of transformation or result so we
got to understand who are we helping
what problems do they have what
Solutions can I bring to them and then
we work backwards from there in
everything that we do to then attract
those people and we want to go based on
the Practical aspect of what those
people want not just the Ethereal or
methodologies or things like that what
are the very practical things that
people desire and that they are looking
for and if you're not promoting your
business you're falling flat because
you're not reaching new people and
connecting with people around that thing
that you can help people with you're
promoting the fact that you can produce
a result that you are promising to this
person and then what happens is the
algorithm then shows your content so
step number one one this is market
research step number two this is
actually putting it in front of these
people right here okay and then once you
put it in front of these people we go to
step number three which is to close the
sale most people never get to this step
because they never even get to this step
where they're not even promoting it but
if you are promoting it to the right
people now we got to figure out okay in
our communication of what we are
promoting it needs to close the sale it
can't just be good information it can't
just get engagement it can't just get a
couple of likes and follows and shares
and things like that it has to get
people to take action and exchange
finances with you and so this is the big
picture of the three-step client
attraction formula that I have that
we've developed that we teach in my
wealthy coach Academy program formerly
known as the client growth accelerator
program we've now renamed it to the
wealthy coach Academy because that's
what we're doing we're helping coaches
mentors and trainers become extremely
wealthy in their life and I'd love to
see you become a part of our wealthy
coach Academy become of our community to
be able to do that in your life and in
your business now one of the number one
things that we have to do to take
somebody from social media to closing a
sale people are skeptical on social
media so what we have to do is we have
to create safety we have to create a
safe environment where people trust that
you're a good person that you deliver on
your word that you can produce the
transformation that you say that you're
going to do and when people trust that
they feel safe enough to exchange
finances with you or exchange their time
with you the reason why most coaches and
mentors don't make the kind of money
they want to make is they are not
connecting with their Prospect and
producing safety in the interaction
they're not creating a safe environment
for these people to take action to move
forward and so that's what we got to do
we got to show people that Hey listen
maybe you've tried this before maybe
you've attempted to do something like
this before but now we can do it in a
way that's going to work for you it's
going to produce a result people want to
know that it's going to get them results
if they're going to take action and so
to attract the right client it's all of
that you want to find where they exist
and then you promote to that group of
people and then once you promote to that
group of people you use what you
promoted what you pushed out there as a
tool as a mechanism to close the sale
and to close the sale it's all about
building Trust it's all about getting
somebody to
believe and trust that you can deliver
on what you say you're going to do that
you're going to get them that result the
only reason why people are going to make
an investment with you is they have a
desired result something they want to
happen in their life they trust that you
can make that happen for them all right
so when it comes to attracting clients
that's what we got to learn how to do
and in my wealthy coach Academy we work
with you through doing that listen I'd
love to see you jump in with us in there
but I'd also love you to share this
podcast with somebody if you're a coach
or Mentor we have a library of trainings
and classes that can help raise you up
to the next level of where you want to
go in your business so make sure you
share it don't keep it to yourself share
this podcast with at least one person
this week we'll talk in everybody grow
your life
[Music]
[Applause]